

NAME
Grzegorz Ostapczuk

↑ PLACE OF RESIDENCE
 Białystok, Poland

GITHUB
github.com/G-Ost

E-MAIL
g.ostapczuk@gmail.com

PHONE NUMBER+48 691 835 187

WEBSITE
grzegorz-ostapczuk-website.web.app

My first contact with programming was during my physics studies (basic C++, Java and JavaScript). Over time, I found that progressing in this direction gave me more satisfaction than physics. For over a year, I have been developing my JavaScript programming skills (mainly React) with the support of experts during postgraduate studies and on my own (Pluralsight courses). I think that the analytical thinking developed while learning physics will be very useful for me as a programmer.

SKILLS

Js JavaS

JavaScript (TypeScript)

F HTML

Node JS

Scrum methodology

React library



CSS



Postman



English (C1)

EDUCATION

10/2020 - Present- Białystok Technical University , JavaScript Developer, Postgraduate studies 10/2018 - 08/2020- University of Białystok, Physics, Masters 10/2013 - 06/2018 - University of Białystok, Physics, Bachelor

EXPERIENCE

TEAM research project of the University of Białystok project member | 09/2018 - 08/2020

Research on new technologies of photomagnetic data recording in a project with a budget exceeding 3 million PLN. Performing physical measurements and advanced data analysis using the Wolfram Mathematica software. Work in a team of 6 people. Presenting the obtained results during seminars and creating reports on scientific activities.

Delta Contact

Customer service telephone consultant | 04/2017 - 09/2017

Customer service, sales, technical support.

PROJECTS

Personal website (JavaScript, React) - https://grzegorz-ostapczuk-website.web.app

Reflex training game (JavaScript, React) - https://gost-reflex-app.web.app/

ToDo App (JavaScript, React) - https://todoapp-1b434.web.app/

Conway's Game of Life (simulation) (JavaScript, React)- https://gost-game-of-life.web.app/

All available on github - github.com/G-Ost

I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation)

-	\sim	~ A	TATE	7 A T	IONS
	112	I _ /		<i>-</i>	

Activity in the student organization AIESEC:

Vice President responsible for incoming global internships programme 02/2016 - 02/2017

Financial supervision over the area in the organization (submitting financial reports, approving budgets of nine projects), sales (over 20 sales meetings, over 100 calls made to companies), market research (over 200 potential leads), managing the sales structure (15 people) and projects language workshops (19 people), conducting sales trainings (over 20 hours), customer service (7 companies), supervising the recruitment and assisting in the visa process of foreign interns for internships in Poland (22 people).

Sales coordinator (national) 02/2016 - 07/2016

Managing a committee of local sales project coordinators (19 people), implementation and standardization of sales knowledge in the network, representing organizations during networking events (Wolves Summit).

AIESEC University language workshops project coordinator (locally) 09/2015 - 04/2016

Managing the finances of the workshops (5000 PLN of the budget, 15000 PLN of revenue). Supervising the recruitment of foreign interns (4 recruited people), team management (4 members), customer service (233 participants).

Science Club of Physicists at the University of Białystok

President 2014 - 2016

Acquiring and managing the organization's funds, active participation and supervision over the research projects of the club, representing the club at the conference, submitting reports on the work of the circle to the university authorities.

PUBLICATIONS

1. K. Rećko, J. Waliszewski, U. Klekotka, D. Soloviov, G. Ostapczuk, D. Satuła, M. Biernacka, M. Balasoiu, A. Basa, B. Kalska-Szostko, K. Szymański, "**Phase composition and magnetism of sol–gel synthesized Ga–Fe–O nanograins"**, Phase Transitions, 91:2, 128-139 (2018).

2. E. Borawska, G. Ostapczuk, "The influence of selected ions on the cloudiness of tea", post conference materials, Notebooks of the Student Scientific Movement of The Jan Kochanowski University in Kielce, 22 (2014).